Mss.B.F327
American Philosophical Society
- William Ellery, 1793 February 24, May 18, 1794 June 13; No. 311
- Andrew Elliot and the Magistrates of the Police to all whom it may concern, 1780 July 21; No. 312
- Oliver Ellsworth to Rufus King, 1801 March 19; No. 313
- Samuel Elmore to Benedict Arnold, 1775 June 11; No. 314
- Roger Enos to Stephen R. Bradley, 1802 March 10; No. 315
- David Stewart Erskine, Lord Buchan to Tobias Lear?, 1794 January 28; No. 316
- John Erving to Godfrey Malbone, 1774 December 24; No. 317
- Charles-Henri-Thedat, Comte d'Estaing to ________, 1782 October 30; No. 318
- Charles-Henri-Thedat, Comte d'Estaing to ________, 1780? November 4; No. 319
- Thomas Etherington, 1785 February 7; No. 320
- James Ettredge, 1800 June 24; No. 321
- Samuel Everett to Luke Drury, 1781 October 11; No. 322
- Lord Thomas Fairfax to Francis Thornton, 1747 January 26; No. 323
- Lord Thomas Fairfax to George Neavil, 1750 November 20; No. 324
- Lord Thomas Fairfax to Amos Janney, 1741 March 13; No. 325
- Lewis Farmer to the Supreme Executive Council of Pennsylvania, 1779 June 7; No. 326
- William Faucitt, 1776 February 26-May 18; No. 327
- Colony of Virginia, Governor Francis Fauquier to James McDowell, 1759 August 15; No. 328
- Christian Febiger to John Nicholson, 1790 June 21; No. 329
- Adam Ferguson to Thomas Barrow, 1778 September 2; No. 330
- Edward Fettyplace to Jonathan Titcomb, 1783 May 1; No. 331
- Nicholas Fish to All whom it may concern, 1777 May 30; No. 332
- Ezekiel Fitch and Isaac Fitch, No. 333
- Colony of Connecticut, Governor Thomas Fitch to Edmund Wells, 1757 February 21; No. 334
- John Fitzgerald to Tench Tilghman and Company, 1784 September 30; No. 335
- Samuel Flaningam, 1780 July 31; No. 336
- Rev. Peter Fontaine to his brothers Moses and John Fontaine, 1756 March 2; No. 337
- Peter Fontaine Jr. to Moses Fontaine, 1754 June 7; No. 338
- Rev. Peter Fontaine to Moses Fontaine, 1757 March 30; No. 339
- Peter Fontaine Jr. to his uncle Moses Fontaine, 1757 June 11; No. 340
- Jean-Marie Bastard, Chavalier de Fontenay to Adam-Phillippe, comte de Custine, 1789 February 9; No. 341
- Uriah Forrest, 1804 April 23; No. 342
- Fort McHenry, 1813 August 2-December 18; No. 343; 2.0 vols.
- Tench Francis to William Seton, 1791 November 23; No. 344
- Benjamin Franklin to John Jay, 1781 April 12; No. 345
- Benjamin Franklin, William Bollan and Arthur Lee to the Speaker of the Rhode Island Assembly Metcalf Bowler, 1774 December 24; No. 346
- Benjamin Franklin to John Wright, 1788 March 31; No. 347
- Benjamin Franklin to the cashier of the bank, n.d.; No. 348
- Benjamin Franklin to the Royal Treasury of France, 1781 October 1; No. 349
- Joshua Freeman, Ambrose Dyer, and Ephraim Harding, Committee of Correspondence to the Committee of Correspondence of the Town of Sandwich, Mass., 1774 January 31; No. 350
- Massachusetts, Provincial Congress, 1775 April 28; No. 351
- Christopher Gadsden to Messrs. LeRoy and Bayard, No. 352
- Thomas Gage to Abraham Mortier, 1768 April 11; No. 353
- Thomas Gage to ________, 1765 July 17; No. 354
- James Gambier to Paul Henry Curry, 1780 April 12; No. 355
- James Gambier to Paul Henry Curry, 1780 May 14; No. 356
- Henry Gardner to Caleb Davis, 1779 September 1; No. 357
- John Garzia to Henry Jackson, 1778 December 2; No. 358
- John Garzia to Henry Jackson, 1778 December 16; No. 359
- Horatio Gates to George Godfrey, 1779 July 26; No. 360
- Horatio Gates to Henry Hollingsworth, 1778 March 24; No. 361
- Horatio Gates to Charles Lee, 1774 July 1, August 17; No. 362
- Horatio Gates to Charles Lee, 1776 January 22; No. 363
- Horatio Gates to Alexander McDougall, 1779 May 26; No. 364
- Horatio Gates to Robert Morris, 1775 July 5; No. 365
- Horatio Gates to Richard Peters, 1783 February 20; No. 366
- Horatio Gates to Artemus Ward, 1775 December 11; No. 367
- Horatio Gates to Benjamin Stelle, 1779 May 17; No. 368
- David Geddes to Thomas Harley and Henry Drummond, 1780 March 6; No. 369
- George III, King of Great Britain to Charles Gallot, 1764 August 23; No. 370
- George III, King of Great Britain to Our General and Commander in Chief of Our Forces in North America (Thomas Gage) or to the Officer Commanding Our said Forces for the time being, 1767 March 26; No. 371
- George III, King of Great Britain to Lord George Germain, 1775 December 25; No. 372
- George III, King of Great Britain to ________, 1789 April 11; No. 373
- George III, King of Great Britain to Thomas Townshend, 1782 December 15; No. 374
- State of Georgia, Chatham County Court to the sheriffs, 1784 March 3; No. 375
- State of Georgia, Montgomery County Court, 1799 April 18; No. 376
- State of Georgia, Richmond County Court to the sheriffs, February 26; No. 377
- State of Georgia, Richmond County Court to the sheriffs, 1784 December 23; No. 378
- Frederick William Geyer to Ward Chipman, 1782 February 2; No. 379
- Jonathan D. Sergeant to Joseph Bloomfield, on behalf of William Coxe, 1792 March 26; No. 380
- John Gill, 1785 October 11; No. 381
- John Taylor Gilman to the sheriff of Hillsborough County, N.H., 1785 March 5; No. 382
- Mordecai Gist to Horatio Gates, 1780 October 4; No. 383
- D______ Godfrey to Turbutt? Francis, 1778 January 3; No. 384
- Armand-Louis de Gontaut, duc de Lauzun and duc de Biron to _______, 1789 January 22; No. 385
- Armand-Louis de Gontaut, duc de Lauzun (later duc de Biron) to Alexandre-Marie-Leonor de Saint Mauris, prince de Montbarey, 1779 November 11; No. 386
- Armand-Louis de Gontaut, duc de Lauzun and duc de Biron to ________, 1789 June 29; No. 387
- Armand-Louis de Gontaut, duc de Lauzun and duc de Biron to ________, 1789 September 3; No. 388
- Nathaniel Goodwin to the Committee of Supplies, 1775 July 31; No. 389
- Rev. William Gordon to Moses Wheelock, 1779 September 16; No. 390
- Aaron Graham to Moses Woodward, 1781 September 10; No. 391
- Charles Graham to Edward Dunscomb, 1783 April 22; No. 392
- Frederick Grando to Robert Rogers, 1761 April 21; No. 393
- John Grant to Sir George Yonge, 1789 September 16; No. 394
- John Grant to Sir George Yonge, 1790 February 24; No. 395
- John Grant to Sir George Yonge, 1789 July; No. 396
- Francois-Joseph-Paul, comte de Grasse to his nephew the comte de Grasse, n.d.; No. 397
- Francois-Joseph-Paul, comte de Grasse to M. LeComte du Bar, 1753 March 25; No. 398
- Rachel Gratz to her father, Bernard Gratz, 1779 August 3; No. 399
- Samuel Graves to the inhabitants of the town of Marshfield, Mass., 1775; No. 400
- Thomas Graves to James Gambier?, 1780 April 12; No. 401
- Ebenezer Gray to John Sumner, 1780 September 21; No. 402
- Ellis Gray, 1768 August 25; No. 403
- Silas Gray to Edward Dunscomb, 1783 October 10; No. 404
- George III, King of Great Britain to William Mecham, 1779 February 22; No. 405
- Great Britain, Parliament, 1782; No. 406
- George III, King of Great Britain, 1780 December 27; No. 407
- George Marlay, 1779 September 12; No. 408
- Great Britain, Army, 1776 February 12-1778 June 28; No. 409; 1.0 vol.
- Great Britain, Admiralty, 1775 June 24; No. 410
- Great Britain, Admiralty, 1777 November 24; No. 411
- Great Britain, Admiralty, 1775 March 13; No. 412
- Great Britain, Admiralty, 1775 June 21; No. 413
- John Montagu Lord Sandwich, Wilmot Vaughan Lord Lisburne, and Sir Hugh Palliser to Hugh Percy, Duke of Northumberland, 1776 November 4; No. 414
- Great Britain, Admiralty, n.d.; No. 415
- Great Britain, Admiralty, 1775 March; No. 416
- George III, King of Great Britain, in Council, 1775 November 22; No. 417
- Colony of East Florida, Court of Vice Admiralty to John Haley, 1779 March 5; No. 418
- Colony of East Florida, Court of Vice Admiralty to John Haley, 1777 January 22; No. 419
- Colony of Connecticut, New London County Court to the sheriff, 1742/43 January 6; No. 420
- Colony of Pennsylvania, Westmoreland County Court to the sheriff, 1774 July 7; No. 421
- Lord George Townshend to Sir Jeffrey Amherst, 1776 April 17; No. 422
- John Morley Green to Henry Jackson, 1778 October 3; No. 423
- Christopher Greene, and thirty-three others to Sir Guy Carleton, 1776 June 7; No. 424
- Nathanael Greene to Henry Hollingsworth, 1779 August 29; No. 425
- Nathanael Greene to Henry Hollingsworth, 1779 December 10; No. 426
- Nathanael Greene to Henry Hollingsworth, 1780 January 29; No. 427
- Nathanael Greene to Henry Hollingsworth, 1780 February 26; No. 428
- Nathanael Greene to Henry Hollingsworth, 1780 May 7; No. 429
- Nathanael Greene to Henry Lee, 1781 December 21; No. 430
- Nathanael Greene, on behalf of the Corporation of Hudson, New York to the mayor Abraham Yates, Jr., 1793 September 25; No. 431
- Nathanael Greene to Andrew Erwin, 1781 October 21; No. 432
- Nathanael Greene to Robert McCorkle, 1781 August 10; No. 433
- ________ to Thomas? Greenleaf, 1793; No. 434
- Charles Grey to ________, 1786 March 10; No. 435
- David Grier to George Washington, 1777 May 18; No. 436
- Thomas Grosvenor, 1779 October 4-5; No. 437
- Benjamin Guerarde to John Hancock, 1783 October 6; No. 438
- Francis Gurney to "Jesse" Jasper Yeates, 1776 June 26; No. 439
- James Guthrie to John Wilkins, Jr., 1799 September 1; No. 440
- James Habersham to John Habersham, 1776 October 26; No. 441
- James Habersham to his brother John Habersham, 1777 March 23; No. 442
- James Habersham to John Habersham, "1778" 1779 January 8; No. 443
- James Habersham to John Habersham, 1780 December 6; No. 444
- James Habersham to John Habersham, 1782 January 13; No. 445
- James Habersham to John Habersham, 1782 February 8; No. 446
- James Habersham to John Habersham, 1782 May 13; No. 447
- James Habersham to John Habersham, 1782 November 13; No. 448
- James Habersham to John Habersham, 1787 January 11; No. 449
- James Habersham to his brother, John Habersham, 1787 October 2; No. 450
- Thomas Hale to his father and mother, 1776 September 13; No. 451
- Jeremiah Halsey to Moore Furman, 1779 June 29; No. 452
- Alexander Hamilton, 1783-1791 May 1; No. 453
- Alexander Hamilton to the collectors of the customs, 1793 March 29; No. 454
- Alexander Hamilton, 1797; No. 455
- Alexander Hamilton, on behalf of Robert Dunbar, 1787 April 21; No. 456
- Alexander Hamilton, 1801?; No. 457
- Alexander Hamilton to the Governor of New Hampshire, Josiah Bartlett, 1793 November 13; No. 458
- Alexander Hamilton to William R. Boote, 1799 March 16; No. 459
- Alexander Hamilton to John Cochran, 1794 March 24; No. 460
- Alexander Hamilton to the collectors of the customs, 1790 September 23; No. 461
- Alexander Hamilton to the collectors of the customs, 1791 September 20; No. 462
- Alexander Hamilton to Sharp Delany, 1789 September 13; No. 463
- Alexander Hamilton to William Ellery, 1790 September 27; No. 464
- Alexander Hamilton to William Ellery, 1790 October 7; No. 465
- Alexander Hamilton to William Ellery, 1793 December 18; No. 466
- Alexander Hamilton to William Ellery, 1794 April 3; No. 467
- Alexander Hamilton to William Ellery, 1794 August 21; No. 468
- Alexander Hamilton to Elizabeth Schuyler, 1780 September 3; No. 469
- Alexander Hamilton to Elizabeth Schuyler, 1781 July 10; No. 470
- Alexander Hamilton to Samuel Hodgdon, 1793 April 17; No. 471
- Alexander Hamilton to Samuel Hodgdon, 1793 September 25; No. 472
- Alexander Hamilton to Nicholas Low, 1796 October 12; No. 473
- Alexander Hamilton to Nicholas Low, 1803 June 17; No. 474
- Alexander Hamilton to James McHenry, 1798 October 19; No. 475
- Alexander Hamilton to James McHenry, 1798 December 17; No. 476
- Alexander Hamilton to James McHenry, 1799 March 14; No. 477
- Alexander Hamilton to James McHenry, 1800 March 17; No. 478
- Alexander Hamilton to James McHenry, 1799 March 18; No. 479
- Alexander Hamilton to James McHenry, 1799 July 29; No. 480
- Alexander Hamilton to James McHenry, 1799 August 5; No. 481
- Alexander Hamilton to James McHenry, 1800 March 26; No. 482
- Alexander Hamilton to James McHenry, 1800 May 15; No. 483
- Alexander Hamilton to James McHenry, 1800 May 23; No. 484
- Alexander Hamilton to James McHenry, 1800 June 6; No. 485
- Alexander Hamilton to James McHenry, 1800 November 13; No. 486
- Alexander Hamilton to James McHenry, 1800 November 22; No. 487
- Alexander Hamilton to Moses Ogden, 1799 September 25; No. 488
- Alexander Hamilton to Richard Platt, 1781 February 25; No. 489
- Alexander Hamilton to William Short, 1790 September 10; No. 490
- Alexander Hamilton to Stephen Smith, 1789 December 4; No. 491
- Alexander Hamilton to Thomas Smith, 1793 May 6; No. 492
- Alexander Hamilton to William Stephens Smith, 1799 October 4; No. 493
- Alexander Hamilton to Jeremiah Wadsworth, 1789 November 8; No. 494
- Alexander Hamilton to Jeremiah Wadsworth, 1793 September 3; No. 495
- Alexander Hamilton to Jeremiah Wadsworth, 1797 June 16; No. 496
- Alexander Hamilton to Jeremiah Wadsworth, 1797 July 28; No. 497
- Alexander Hamilton to Jeremiah Wadsworth, 1801 March 25; No. 498
- Alexander Hamilton to Jeremiah Wadsworth, 1801 May 8; No. 499
- Alexander Hamilton to Elie Williams, 1789 October 17; No. 500
- Alexander Hamilton to Ortho Holland Williams, 1789 November 7; No. 501
- Alexander Hamilton to Abraham Yates, Jr., 1793 September 26; No. 502
- Alexander Hamilton to Lieutenant colonels, 1799 July 22; No. 503
- Alexander Hamilton to ________, No. 504
- Trustees of the estate of Alexander Hamilton to William Rogers, 1804 November 29; No. 505
- Elizabeth Schuyler Hamilton to Dr. ______ McDonald, 1831 June 16; No. 506
- John Hamilton to Jacob Read, 1792 March 5; No. 507
- George Hammond to the Secretary of State, Edmund Randolph, 1795 March 3; No. 508
- Wade Hampton to Messrs. Miller and Robertson, 1795 May 23; No. 509
- United States, Continental Congress (John Hancock, President) to William Stewart, 1778 February 1; No. 510
- John Hancock to "Dolly" (Dorothy Quincy Hancock), 1778 August 10; No. 511
- John Hancock to Oliver Prescott, 1779 September 13; No. 512
- John Hancock to the President Thomas Wharton, Jr. and Council of Pennsylvania, 1777 April 2; No. 513
- United States, Continental Congress (John Hancock, President), 1775 July 31; No. 514
- Edward Hand, 1783 January 29; No. 515
- Edward Hand to Charles Gordon, 1782 February 27; No. 516
- James Hannah to John Beal Howard, 1774 February 5; No. 517
- Lord William Harcourt, 1811 January 28; No. 518
- George Lechler, 1794 April; No. 519
- Benjamin Harrison to Lachlan McIntosh?, 1778 August 27; No. 520
- Robert Hanson Harrison to George Washington, 1780 April 6; No. 521
- James Grant, 1776 December 12; No. 522
- John Hart for John and Frederick Strosnyder, 1765 December 20; No. 523
- Thomas Hartley to Edward Hand, 1779 May 10; No. 524
- John Hartwell to Samuel Holten, 1785 October 15; No. 525
- Benjamin Hawes to ________, 1778 June 19; No. 526
- Richard Howly to Anthony Wayne, 1782 June; No. 527
- Robert Young Hayne, 1827 January 30; No. 528; Hayne's presentation in Congress of the petition of Thomas Jefferson Randolph that requests an act to permit a lottery to be held to dispose of the estate of Thomas Jefferson at its appraised value for the benefit of the latter's daughter [Martha Jefferson Randolph].
  General note
  David Library Item Number: 528; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- Robert Young Hayne to Nicholas Biddle, 1827 February 15; No. 529
- John Hazelwood to William Watkins, 1777 January 6; No. 530
- Moses Hazen to Benjamin Lincoln, 1782 June; No. 531
- Frederick William Hecht to William Shirreff, 1775 May 4; No. 532
- William Heath to Ezra Badlam, 1780 February 19; No. 533
- William Heath to Ebenezer Hancock, 1777 April 12; No. 534
- William Heath to Edward Hand, 1782 January 8; No. 535
- William Heath to David Henley, 1789 March 24; No. 536
- John Covenhoven, David Forman, and Thomas Henderson to William Livingston, 1782 July 20; No. 537
- Patrick Henry to George Washington, 1777 September 8; No. 538
- William Henshaw to John Southgate, 1786 September 19; No. 539
- W______ Hewson to ________, 1775 March; No. 540
- Henry Hill to All whom it may concern, 1776 July 9; No. 541
- Michael Hillegas to Elbridge Gerry, 1777 May 3; No. 542
- Jacob Hiltzheimer, 1780 May 5; No. 543
- George Hobart to ________, 1779 December 20; No. 544
- Samuel Holten, 1778 May 4-1780 August 23; No. 545
- Sir Samuel Hood to Captain ______ Graves, 1782 April 23; No. 546
- Stephen Hooper to John Reynell and Samuel Coates, 1775 April 25; No. 547
- Stephen Hooper to John Reynell and Samuel Coates, 1775 June 1; No. 548
- Stephen Hooper to John Reynell and Samuel Coates, 1775 September 19; No. 549
- Stephen Hooper to John Reynell and Samuel Coates, 1775 October 21; No. 550
- Stephen Hooper to John Reynell and Samuel Coates, 1776 February 20, 23; No. 551
- Stephen Hooper to John Reynell and Samuel Coates, 1776 August 27; No. 552
- Stephen Hooper to John Reynell and Samuel Coates, 1777 January 13; No. 553
- Stephen Hooper to John Reynell and Samuel Coates, 1777 March 12; No. 554
- Joseph Hopkins, 1780 August 5, 7; No. 555
- Joseph Hopkinson to William Young, n.d.; No. 556
- Massachusetts, Town of Scituate, 1777 June 23; No. 557
- John Eager Howard to Henry Hollingsworth, 1789 May 8; No. 558
- John Howe? to John Fisher, 1716/17 January 7; No. 559
- Lord Richard Howe to John Douglas, 1782 June 7; No. 560
- Lord Richard Howe to William Eden, 1778 July 9; No. 561
- Lord Richard Howe, Charles Brett, and Richard Hopkins to Thomas Townshend, 1788 April 24; No. 562
- Robert Howe to ________, 1780 April 29; No. 563
- Sir William Howe to Matthew Lewis, 1790 December 12; No. 564
- James Grant, 1776 December 12; No. 565
- Jacob S. Howell to the commissioners appointed by the Convention of Pennsylvania to form the Flying Camp, 1776 August 19; No. 566
- State of New Jersey, Governor Richard Howell, 1794 May 1; No. 567
- Garnet Hughes to Lambert Cadwalader, 1775 August 2; No. 568
- Hugh Hughes to David Wolfe, 1781 March 4; No. 569
- Hugh Hughes to David Wolfe, 1781 March 21; No. 570
- Hugh Hughes to David Wolfe, 1781 November 6; No. 571
- Hugh Hughes to David Wolfe, 1782 March 20; No. 572
- Hugh Hughes to David Wolfe, 1782 June 5; No. 573
- Hugh Hughes to David Wolfe, 1782 June 18; No. 574
- Hugh Hughes to David Wolfe, 1782 July 10; No. 575
- Hugh Hughes to David Wolfe, 1782 December 28; No. 576
- David Humphreys to Nathanael Greene, 1780 May 23; No. 577
- David Humphreys to Rev. Enos Hitchcock, 1800 April 28; No. 578
- Richard Hunewell, 1796 July 7; No. 579
- Thomas Hunt to Edward Dunscomb, 1783 April 20; No. 580
- Benjamin Huntington to the Committee of Pay-Table, 1777 April 15; No. 581
- Ebenezer Huntington to Joshua Huntington, 1778 September 4; No. 582
- Jedediah Huntington to Andrew Huntington, No. 583
  Microfilm target that describes the following fifteen letters.
- Jedediah Huntington to Andrew Huntington, 1776 March 13; No. 584
- Jedediah Huntington to Andrew Huntington, 1776 August 6; No. 585
- Jedediah Huntington to Andrew Huntington, 1776 October 20; No. 586
- Jedediah Huntington to Jabez Huntington, 1775 November 11; No. 587
- Jedediah Huntington to Jabez Huntington, 1775 December 4; No. 588
- Jedediah Huntington to Jabez Huntington, 1775 December 25; No. 589
- Jedediah Huntington to Jabez Huntington, 1776 January 18; No. 590
- Jedediah Huntington to Jabez Huntington, 1776 February 13; No. 591
- Jedediah Huntington to Jabez Huntington, 1776 February 19; No. 592
- Jedediah Huntington to Jabez Huntington, 1776 July 29, August 3; No. 593
- Jedediah Huntington to Jabez Huntington, 1776 September 28; No. 594
- Jedediah Huntington to Jabez Huntington, 1776 October 15; No. 595
- Jedediah Huntington to Jabez Huntington, 1776 November 8; No. 596
- Jedediah Huntington to Jabez Huntington, 1776 December 11, 28; No. 597
- Jedediah Huntington to Jabez Huntington, 1778 May 17; No. 598
- Jedediah Huntington to Jabez Huntington, 1779 March 3; No. 599
- Richard Kimball to Samuel Huntington, 1782? April; No. 600
- Samuel Huntington to Richard Howly, 1780 August 9; No. 601
- Samuel Huntington to Jabez Huntington, 1778 April 19; No. 602
- Samuel Huntington to the President of Delaware (Caesar Rodney), 1780 June 15; No. 603
- Samuel Huntington to Benjamin Lincoln, 1780 January 8; No. 604
- State of Connecticut, New London County Court to the sheriff or constables, 1789 March 12; No. 605
- State of Connecticut, New Haven County Court to the sheriffs or constables, 1777 March 15; No. 606
- State of Connecticut, New Haven County Court to the sheriffs or constables, 1777 March 17; No. 607
- State of Connecticut, Windham County Court to the sheriff or constables, 1789 July 15; No. 608
- State of Connecticut, Windham County Court to the sheriff or constables, 1790 January 26; No. 609
- State of Connecticut, Windham County Court to the sheriff or constables, 1790 January 26; No. 610
- ________ to Thomas Hutchinson, 1775 August 20; No. 611
- United States, Oath of Allegiance, 1776-1783; No. 612
- Jared Ingersoll to Jasper Yeates, 1787 February 20; No. 613
- James Irvine to David Rittenhouse, 1785 April 18; No. 614
- William Irvine to ________, 1776 March 5; No. 615
- Matthew Irwin to John Barclay, 1793 September 30; No. 616
- Henry Jackson to Charles Stewart, 1782 May 6; No. 617
- Henry Jackson to John Sullivan, 1778 December 1; No. 618
- Henry Jackson to George Washington, 1777 February 1; No. 619
- United States, Continental Army, Henry Jackson's regiment, Committee of officers to the committee from Generals John Nixon's, John Glover's, John Paterson's and late Ebenezer Learned's Brigades, 1778 November 26; No. 620
- James Jackson to John Milledge, 1794 January 31; No. 621
- John Jackson to Henry Jackson, 1778 November 7; No. 622
- Thomas Frederick Jackson to the Commissary General of Forage or his deputies, 1780 September 28, 30; No. 623
- James I, King of England to the Escheator in the County of Warwick, 1604/05 February 5; No. 624
- David Jamison to Governor William Burnet?, 1722 March 29; No. 625
- John Jay, 1775 December 11; No. 626
- John Jay to Anne-Cesar, chevalier de La Luzerne, 1779 January 22; No. 627
- Thomas Jefferson to ________, n.d.; No. 628
- Thomas Jefferson to Theodorick Bland, 1780 January 18; No. 629
- Thomas Jefferson to John Breckenridge, 1800 July 4; No. 630
- Thomas Jefferson to William S. Cardell, 1820 March 8; No. 631; Because of continued ill-health "with one foot in the grave" defers to "youthful minds" regarding a new enterprise.
  David Library Item Number: 631; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- Thomas Jefferson to Thomas Carstairs, 1798 April 9; No. 632
- Thomas Jefferson to William Channing, 1790 August 12; No. 633
- Thomas Jefferson to Joseph Francisco Correa da Serra, 1817 June 14; No. 634; Expresses hope that since da Serra will reside in the vicinity, he will visit Jefferson; informs him when Jefferson will be at Poplar Forest, [Va.] annually "while strength enough remains"; mentions that the President [James Monroe] expects to be on a Northern Tour for approximately two months.
  David Library Item Number: 634; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- Thomas Jefferson to Henry Dearborn, 1801 July 28; No. 635
- Thomas Jefferson to James Dinsmore, 1808 December 11; No. 636
- Thomas Jefferson to Charles William Frederick Dumas, 1792 November 14; No. 637
- Thomas Jefferson to Jean Durival, 1789 April 13; No. 638
- Thomas Jefferson to Dr. William Eustis, 1812 June 6; No. 639; Informs him about "the exposed state" of a magazine located near New London, [Va.], where there are many "grumblers and malcontents" and recommends the removal of stores to Lynchburg, [Va.].
  David Library Item Number: 639; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- Thomas Jefferson to "John" Giovanni Fabbroni, 1778 June 8; No. 640
- Thomas Jefferson to John H. Freeman, 1805 November 16; No. 641